(Howard:)slightly... bigger
cocktail umbrellas.
(Leonard:)How is that a new invention?
(Howard:)I don't know, all Apple does
is change the size of things
(Howard:)and we keep buying them.
(Raj:)It's true. I like my giant iPad
and my little iPad
(Raj:)almost as much
as my regular-sized iPad.
(Sheldon:)This place is terrific.
Why-why have
we never been here before?
(Leonard:)The same reason we don't do
a lot of fun stuff... you.
(Sheldon:)That's some smart talk
from a guy
(Sheldon:)who can't even keep
his face in focus.
(Sheldon:)Where's the bathroom?
(Raj:)Uh, it's in the corner.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me.
(Sheldon:)Hey, how you doin'?
(Raj:)I hope the bathroom
is clearly marked.
(Leonard:)Doesn't matter.
(Leonard:)He's headed
for the kitchen anyway.
(Howard:)Maybe that's an idea...
(Howard:)guidance systems
for drunk people.
(Raj:)They have that.
It's called Uber.
(Leonard:)Hey.